<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NamoGange</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ganga_desc1">The Ganga, especially, is the river of India, beloved of her people,
        round which are intertwined her memories, her hopes and fears, her songs of triumph,
        her victories and her defeats. She has been a symbol of India’s age-long culture and civilization,
        ever changing, ever flowing, and yet ever the same Ganga.-Jawaharlal Nehru</string>
    <string name="ganga_desc2">Ganga River is one of the prime rivers of India and is declared as the
        National River of India. It flows east through the Gangetic plains of Northern India into the
        country of Bangladesh. The river has immense religious significance and considered as the
        holy river of the Hindus. Historically too the river is important as many important cities
        and capitals have been located along its banks. The Ganga sustains one of the world\'s highest
        densities of population and drains an area of approximately 1000000 sq. kms.</string>
    <string name="ganga_desc3">Ganga River originates in the Himalayas and is 2, 510 km (1, 557 meters) long.
        It begins at the Gangotri glacier in the state of Uttarakhand in the central Himalayas at the concourse
        of five headstreams - Bhagirathi River, Mandakini, Alaknanda River, Dhauliganga and Pindar at Dev Prayag.
        Ganga or, more exactly, Bhagirathi, originates from Gangotri glacier,
        one of the biggest glaciers in Himalayas.</string>
    <string name="ganga_article1">The Supreme Court on Wednesday expressed disappointment with the Centre
        for its lack of a long-term vision to clean the river Ganga. Expressing the anguish Justice Thakur
        said: If the discharge of industrial pollutants into the river stooped, 30% of the Ganga would be clean.
        Corruption was stalling the clean Ganga project and heads must roll out for this. The Central Pollution
        Control Board (CPCB), a statutory body which is to take effective steps, is not in a position to stop the
        polluting units from discharging effluents into the river. Units are being allowed to run accepting bribe.
        This is breeding corruption and the board is not doing it work.</string>
    <string name="ganga_article2">According to a study conducted by Anil Kumar Misra (2010), the Yamuna
        is one of the most polluted rivers of India.The discharge of untreated domestic and industrial effluents have severely affected the quality of Yamuna River and now
        it falls under the category E, which makes it fit only for recreation and industrial cooling, completely ruling out the
        possibility for underwater life and domestic supply. Almost every year mass death of fishes is reported. Pollution levels
        in the Yamuna River have risen. Biochemical oxygen demand (BOD) load has increased by 2.5 times between 1980 and 2005:
        From 117 tonnes per day (TDP) in 1980 to 276 TDP in 2005. The Yamuna has been reduced to a small stream, draining
        industrial effluents, sewage, dirt and other toxic substances. There is an urgent need to take stringent measures
        to alleviate these pollution loads and save an ailing river</string>
    <string name="ganga_article3">In Hinduism, the river Ganges is considered sacred and is personified as a goddess known as Ganga. It is worshipped by
        Hindus who believe that bathing in the river causes the remission of sins and facilitates Moksha (liberation from the
        cycle of life and death). Pilgrims travel long distances to immerse the ashes of their kin in the precious water of the
        Ganges, bringing their spirits closer to moksha.<br/><br/>Several places sacred to Hindus lie along the banks of the Ganges,
        including Gangotri, Haridwar, Allahabad and Varanasi.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
</resources>
